{"classes":["ORG","PER","LOCATION","PRODUCTS","DATE & TIME","MONEY","PERCENTAGE","RATIO","VOLUME","CORPORATE ACTIONS","MARKET EVENTS","POSITIVE","NEGATIVE","EQUITIES","BONDS","REGULATIONS"],"annotations":[["ca6831fc-5d75-48c4-acd0-1cf4b017150a\r\nDescription\r\nA senior State Bank of India (SBI) executive said in the case of large corporates, where there is consortium and social ba All analysts tracking it are optimistic on the stock, which hasn't seen any downgrade so far\r\nCII has sought an increase in credit limits for all regular banking accounts by 25 per cent\r\nPublic trust in public sector banks will remain strong, underpinned by a perception of strong government protection for the The approach, according to people familiar with the RBI, is that the regulator can only enable the banks to take such com Some branch staff have complained on social media of the difficulty in imposing social distancing in such conditions, earn Worsening business conditions and sell-off by anchor investors have taken the stock southward\r\nMoody's said the Yes Bank episode places the country's financial system on \"alert\" and the rescue in itself \"exposes wea Muthoot Finance's Ba2 CFR is affirmed and its outlook changed to negative from stable.\r\nFIDC has asked the central bank to extend the facility to all customer loans\r\nThe Asian Development Bank said it has also approved measures to streamline its operations for quicker and more flexib The company's collection efficiency pan-India for the period from January 1, 2020 till March 21, 2020 stands at 98.7 per c Max Life Insurance is a joint venture between Max Financial Services Ltd and Mitsui Sumitomo Insurance\r\nLoans and advances jumped by 60 per cent to Rs 71,825 crore during 2019-20, from Rs 44,776 crore the year before. Sources say PBoC may have increased its stake by 0.2 percentage points in March\r\nIronclad succession process could weigh on extensions for current heads\r\nPNB also has a tie up with Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) for selling its products through the bank's branches According to him, interest rates will go down further, but banks must pass them on to companies.\r\nMost banks are yet to decide on giving moratorium to shadow lenders\r\nIt had said that repayment schedule for such loans as also the residual tenor would be shifted across the board by three These investors are yet to approve the moratorium on underlying loans and reschedule most PTC repayments\r\nMany finance companies are already facing a liquidity challenge after the IL&FS debacle.\r\nDeposit accretion activity also moderated in FY20 to 7.9 per cent from 10 per cent in FY19, according to Reserve Bank of Private sector lenders have been leading on this front for some time, mostly leveraging on retail credit.\r\nBank advances growth in FY20 was the slowest since the fiscal ended March 1962, when loans had grown by 5.38 per ce\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nPage 1\r\n",{"entities":[[60,85,"ORG"],[149,159,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[164,173,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[203,216,"POSITIVE"],[268,271,"ORG"],[348,359,"PERCENTAGE"],[361,373,"POSITIVE"],[377,396,"ORG"],[537,540,"ORG"],[730,759,"NEGATIVE"],[842,850,"ORG"],[870,896,"MARKET EVENTS"],[901,906,"MARKET EVENTS"],[916,922,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[946,971,"ORG"],[1034,1038,"ORG"],[1053,1065,"ORG"],[1066,1088,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[1116,1138,"ORG"],[1297,1306,"DATE & TIME"],[1308,1312,"DATE & TIME"],[1318,1332,"DATE & TIME"],[1354,1372,"ORG"],[1400,1426,"ORG"],[1431,1446,"ORG"],[1487,1498,"PERCENTAGE"],[1502,1511,"MONEY"],[1525,1532,"DATE & TIME"],[1539,1548,"MONEY"],[1621,1635,"PERCENTAGE"],[1726,1729,"ORG"],[1753,1788,"ORG"],[1866,1893,"NEGATIVE"],[1985,1995,"REGULATIONS"],[2175,2185,"REGULATIONS"],[2226,2229,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[2286,2305,"NEGATIVE"],[2316,2330,"MARKET EVENTS"],[2377,2381,"DATE & TIME"],[2385,2397,"PERCENTAGE"],[2403,2414,"PERCENTAGE"],[2418,2422,"DATE & TIME"],[2437,2467,"ORG"],[2486,2507,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[2584,2588,"DATE & TIME"],[2628,2638,"DATE & TIME"],[2664,2675,"VOLUME"]]}]]}