{"classes":["ORG","PER","LOCATION","PRODUCTS","DATE & TIME","MONEY","PERCENTAGE","RATIO","VOLUME","CORPORATE ACTIONS","MARKET EVENTS","POSITIVE","NEGATIVE","EQUITIES","BONDS","REGULATIONS"],"annotations":[["Description\n\"Close to 14.6 per cent (or 35,000) of the 240,000 ATMs in India are new-age recyclers, even though they have been around for only ...\"\n\"V Vaidyanathan, managing director and chief executive, will take 30 per cent cut in his compensation, including fixed ...\"\nRana Kapoor's wife also charged with abetting crime\nThe bank said it was now gearing up to extend the stimulus package announced by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman to restart ...\n\"Net profit for the financial year ended March 31, 2020 (FY20), stood at Rs 337.25 crore, up marginally from Rs 325.37 crore in ...\"\n\"Under the scheme, the government will offer 100 per cent guarantee on loans.\"\nHDFC Bank cuts base rate by 55 bps; SBI calls ALCO meeting to take call\n\"The six-member MPC also kept policy stance unchanged at 'accommodative' for \"\"as long as necessary\"\" to revive growth\"\nThe central bank has increased group exposure limits of lenders from 25% to 30%\nTwo new series will have maturities of April 2025 and April 2031.\nCredit costs could touch Rs 2.7 trillion\nEnquiries for fresh loans see uptick\n\"While slippages from the corporate sector may rise by Rs 3.4 trillion, for non-corporate segments it may increase by Rs 2.1 ...\"\n\"The meeting was earlier scheduled on May 11, but due to the stimulus package announcements, it was deferred, they added\"\n\"In a Q&A, the lender's MD & CEO, Amitabh Chaudhry, also dwells on the stimulus package announced by the government, and risk ...\"\nLoans sanctioned by public sector banks (PSBs) at the end of May 8 stood at Rs 5.95 trillion\nSenior bank executives said the Indian Banks' Association (IBA) has already approached the Reserve Bank of India with a plea for ...\nIt may be time to link the higher deposit insurance cover and the way co-operative banks and select non-banks raise retail ...\nNBFCs cry foul as they were expecting a two-three year support\n\"The only way to boost demand may be lowering interest rates to boost consumption, analysts said\"\n\"PE, VC funds domiciled in the island nation on the radar\"\nLast financial year saw a series of banks failures starting with Punjab & Maharashtra Co-operative Bank and culminated in near ...\n\"These firms operate with very little short-term liquidity, which can become even more strained as customers start defaulting even ...\"\nState-owned banks launched an emergency credit line to provide funds to its existing MSME and corporate borrowers in the last ...\n\"Refinancing high-cost debt into low-cost debt is possible, thanks to the RBI's TLTROs\"\n",{"entities":[[22,35,"PERCENTAGE"],[71,76,"LOCATION"],[81,98,"PRODUCTS"],[148,163,"PER"],[214,225,"PERCENTAGE"],[226,249,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[272,283,"PER"],[309,323,"NEGATIVE"],[328,332,"ORG"],[349,390,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[421,439,"PER"],[496,517,"DATE & TIME"],[528,543,"MONEY"],[545,558,"POSITIVE"],[564,579,"MONEY"],[633,645,"PERCENTAGE"],[646,655,"POSITIVE"],[659,666,"PRODUCTS"],[667,676,"ORG"],[677,691,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[695,701,"PERCENTAGE"],[703,706,"ORG"],[707,725,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[755,758,"ORG"],[764,792,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[844,858,"POSITIVE"],[863,875,"ORG"],[880,911,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[928,931,"PERCENTAGE"],[935,938,"PERCENTAGE"],[978,988,"DATE & TIME"],[993,1004,"DATE & TIME"],[1030,1045,"MONEY"],[1060,1071,"PRODUCTS"],[1076,1082,"POSITIVE"],[1090,1099,"NEGATIVE"],[1109,1125,"PRODUCTS"],[1138,1153,"MONEY"],[1159,1181,"PRODUCTS"],[1201,1207,"MONEY"],[1251,1257,"DATE & TIME"],[1306,1321,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[1369,1385,"PER"],[1392,1422,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[1466,1471,"PRODUCTS"],[1486,1512,"ORG"],[1527,1532,"DATE & TIME"],[1542,1558,"MONEY"],[1591,1622,"ORG"],[1650,1671,"ORG"],[1719,1725,"POSITIVE"],[1726,1749,"PRODUCTS"],[1762,1780,"ORG"],[1792,1801,"ORG"],[1819,1824,"ORG"],[1825,1833,"NEGATIVE"],[1899,1911,"POSITIVE"],[1928,1942,"PRODUCTS"],[1946,1963,"POSITIVE"],[1980,1983,"ORG"],[1985,1993,"ORG"],[2011,2024,"LOCATION"],[2075,2080,"ORG"],[2081,2089,"NEGATIVE"],[2104,2110,"LOCATION"],[2113,2124,"LOCATION"],[2125,2142,"ORG"],[2201,2228,"NEGATIVE"],[2285,2295,"NEGATIVE"],[2306,2323,"ORG"],[2336,2357,"POSITIVE"],[2361,2374,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[2469,2482,"POSITIVE"],[2510,2515,"ORG"],[2516,2523,"PRODUCTS"]]}]]}