{"classes":["ORG","PER","LOCATION","PRODUCTS","DATE & TIME","MONEY","PERCENTAGE","RATIO","VOLUME","CORPORATE ACTIONS","MARKET EVENTS","POSITIVE","NEGATIVE","EQUITIES","BONDS","REGULATIONS"],"annotations":[["Description\r\n\"Larger challenge is to communicate to borrowers the difference between moratorium and waiver, say lenders\"\r\n\"Capital infusion to be supported by IDFC limited, ICICI Prudential Life, HDFC Life, Warburg Pincus and Bajaj Allianz\"\r\n\"On April 27, the RBI had introduced the Rs 50,000-crore liquidity line for the MF industry\"\r\n\"With malls and shops closed, spending avenues are practically non-existent.\"\r\n\"Affirms Issuer Default Ratings for seven banks including these four and Bank of India, Canara and PNB\"\r\n\"Industry has also pitched for SPV with initial funding from govt, to help refinance small and mid-sized NBFCs\"\r\n\"According to informal estimates, the two organisations together are looking to extend Rs 7,000-8,000 crore in funding\"\r\n\"Given the extended lockdown, the bank extensively used its digital platform, including video conferencing, to carry out the ...\"\r\n\"On April 1, Punjab National Bank (PNB) took over Oriental Bank of Commerce (OBC) and United Bank of India (UBI) to become the ...\"\r\nVyas is a senior banking professional with over 36 years of experience in banking across a range of diverse functions in both ...\r\n\"Banks have built internal capacities for assisting companies, including micro, small & medium enterprises (MSMEs).\"\r\nBoth the banks have come together amid the coronavirus (Covid-19) lockdown and started working as a single bank with a larger ...\r\n\"The write-offs are technical or prudential in nature, which means the banks have made 100 per cent provisions against the loans\"\r\nLenders are staring at unexpected asset quality losses due to the slowdown in economic activity after the countrywide lockdown.\r\n\"Axis is looking to purchase around 55.61 crore shares of Max Life Insurance at a price of Rs 28.61 per share, but the estimate ...\"\r\n\"The special repo window, under which banks can borrow up to 90 days to extend loans or buy debt papers of MFs, remains open till ...\"\r\n\"According to the available data, the credit risk fund category saw its assets under management (AUM) dip by another 12 per cent ...\"\r\nPublic sector bank executives point out that banks understand the need to provide critical support to borrowers hit by the ...\r\n\"The lender reported a 45 per cent jump in net interest income at Rs 3,232 crore in Q4 FY20\"\r\nBid and offer pattern shows a healthy market response\r\n\"The duo was arrested on Sunday from a Mahabaleshwar-based quarantine facility, nearly 50 days after they were booked in the case ...\"\r\n\"Banks unwilling to take on credit risk in their balance sheets beyond a point, says central bank governor\"\r\nThe liquidity strains have intensified in the wake of redemption pressures related to closure of some debt MFs and potential ...\r\n\"Covid has caused disruption in the domestic and global markets, enhancing the risk of default from the rise in cost of repayments ...\"\r\nThe RBI had permitted a one-time restructuring of existing loans to GST-registered MSME units\r\n",{"entities":[[85,95,"REGULATIONS"],[100,106,"REGULATIONS"],[122,139,"MARKET EVENTS"],[159,163,"ORG"],[173,178,"ORG"],[196,200,"ORG"],[207,221,"ORG"],[226,240,"ORG"],[242,254,"DATE & TIME"],[260,263,"ORG"],[283,298,"MONEY"],[322,334,"ORG"],[488,501,"ORG"],[503,518,"ORG"],[551,554,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[560,575,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[581,585,"ORG"],[625,631,"ORG"],[720,740,"MONEY"],[765,782,"MARKET EVENTS"],[842,860,"PRODUCTS"],[885,896,"PER"],[898,924,"ORG"],[935,966,"ORG"],[971,997,"ORG"],[1018,1022,"PER"],[1066,1074,"DATE & TIME"],[1149,1155,"ORG"],[1167,1186,"POSITIVE"],[1256,1262,"ORG"],[1276,1281,"ORG"],[1485,1497,"PERCENTAGE"],[1552,1562,"NEGATIVE"],[1577,1583,"NEGATIVE"],[1635,1656,"MARKET EVENTS"],[1658,1663,"ORG"],[1694,1712,"VOLUME"],[1716,1734,"ORG"],[1749,1767,"RATIO"],[1797,1816,"REGULATIONS"],[1853,1860,"DATE & TIME"],[1864,1876,"BONDS"],[1884,1895,"BONDS"],[1899,1902,"ORG"],[2045,2056,"PERCENTAGE"],[2063,2081,"ORG"],[2108,2113,"ORG"],[2145,2161,"POSITIVE"],[2214,2225,"PERCENTAGE"],[2257,2265,"MONEY"],[2275,2283,"DATE & TIME"],[2315,2329,"POSITIVE"],[2340,2348,"PER"],[2353,2371,"NEGATIVE"],[2379,2398,"LOCATION"],[2427,2434,"DATE & TIME"],[2476,2482,"ORG"],[2483,2492,"NEGATIVE"],[2589,2606,"NEGATIVE"],[2639,2659,"MARKET EVENTS"],[2692,2695,"ORG"],[2733,2759,"NEGATIVE"],[2794,2809,"NEGATIVE"],[2856,2859,"ORG"],[2876,2898,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[2920,2934,"REGULATIONS"]]}]]}