{"classes":["ORG","PER","LOCATION","PRODUCTS","DATE & TIME","MONEY","PERCENTAGE","RATIO","VOLUME","CORPORATE ACTIONS","MARKET EVENTS","POSITIVE","NEGATIVE","EQUITIES","BONDS","REGULATIONS","OTHER"],"annotations":[["Description\t",{"entities":[]}],["With collections taking a big hit, microfinance institutions will be put through the wringer, reports Raghu Mohan\t",{"entities":[[35,60,"ORG"],[85,92,"NEGATIVE"],[102,113,"PER"]]}],["There is a facility of standby line of credit for MSMEs as well as PNB COVID-19 Emergency Credit Facility (PNB-CECF), the bank ...\t",{"entities":[[23,45,"PRODUCTS"],[50,55,"ORG"],[67,105,"PRODUCTS"],[122,126,"ORG"]]}],["The lender had psoted a pre-tax loss of Rs 2,338.31 crore in the same quarter of previous financial year\t",{"entities":[[32,36,"NEGATIVE"],[40,57,"MONEY"],[100,104,"DATE & TIME"]]}],["Considers 25 fresh credit proposals from shadow banks\t",{"entities":[[41,53,"ORG"]]}],["The outstanding portfolio of private banks in the credit card space has increased by 59 per cent year-on-year while other issuers ...\t",{"entities":[[29,42,"ORG"],[85,96,"PERCENTAGE"]]}],["Debt of Centre and states combined is over 70% of GDP already\t country is currently just a notch above junk",{"entities":[[0,4,"NEGATIVE"],[43,46,"PERCENTAGE"]]}],["Muted lending and subdued cross-selling amidst extended lockdown to hurt fee income and earnings\t",{"entities":[]}],["Private banks put up a better show than other card financiers\t",{"entities":[[0,13,"ORG"]]}],["Axis' credit costs for the quarter ended March 31, 2020 are higher than anticipated, but some of it is precautionary\t",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"],[41,55,"DATE & TIME"]]}],["Economic slowdown hits activity, adding fuel to the fire\t",{"entities":[[9,17,"NEGATIVE"]]}],["In addition, West Bengal will also request the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to increase the additional credit limit to MSMEs, to ...\t",{"entities":[[13,24,"LOCATION"],[47,74,"ORG"],[118,123,"ORG"]]}],["The motor and health segments led the decline in premiums for the industry as the month saw premium fall by 9 per cent.\t",{"entities":[[38,45,"NEGATIVE"],[100,104,"NEGATIVE"],[108,118,"PERCENTAGE"]]}],["Senior SBI executives said most of those seeking deferment are retail and micro and small enterprises and are hard-pressed for ...\t",{"entities":[[7,10,"ORG"]]}],["Suggestions from various quarters, including from Indian Banks' Association, have come for the further extension of moratorium ...\t",{"entities":[[50,75,"ORG"],[116,126,"REGULATIONS"]]}],["Covid-19 has led to lot of uncertainties including those pertaining to the income level of borrowers and hence, their loan ...\t",{"entities":[]}],["Mutual Funds say they didn't need to use their liquidity line fully\t",{"entities":[[0,12,"PRODUCTS"],[47,61,"OTHER"]]}],["From now on, the system should open up systematically as people's financial cushions could vanish soon, he says\t",{"entities":[[91,97,"NEGATIVE"]]}],["The RBI cancelled the licence of CKP Co-op Bank on April 28, and notified the cancelletaion on its website on Saturday. There it ...\t",{"entities":[[4,7,"ORG"],[8,29,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[33,47,"ORG"],[51,59,"DATE & TIME"]]}],["The number of NPA accounts rose from 2,08,035 as of March 31, 2014, to 6,17,306 as of December 2019\t",{"entities":[[14,17,"OTHER"],[52,66,"DATE & TIME"],[86,99,"DATE & TIME"]]}],["Relaxation likely on branch audit as Guv meets bankers\t",{"entities":[[21,33,"REGULATIONS"],[37,40,"PER"]]}],["Depositors to get up to Rs 5 lakh under deposit insurance on liquidation\t",{"entities":[[24,33,"MONEY"],[40,57,"REGULATIONS"],[61,72,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"]]}],["The meetings were also attended by deputy governors and other senior officers of the central bank, RBI said in a statement on its ...\t",{"entities":[[35,51,"PER"],[99,102,"ORG"]]}],["Dhawan will assume charge from Saturday in place of Ashish Agarwal, the current chief risk officer, who will be transitioning to ...\t",{"entities":[[0,6,"PER"],[31,39,"DATE & TIME"],[52,66,"PER"]]}],["Fitch has cut its forecast for India's GDP growth in the financial year ending March 2021 (FY21) to 0.8 per cent from a ...\t",{"entities":[[0,5,"OTHER"],[39,42,"OTHER"],[43,49,"POSITIVE"],[79,89,"DATE & TIME"],[100,112,"PERCENTAGE"]]}],["The meeting will take stock of implementation of several steps announced by the RBI, including moderation in interest rate and ...\t",{"entities":[[80,83,"ORG"],[95,122,"OTHER"]]}],["",{"entities":[]}]]}