{"classes":["ORG","PER","LOCATION","PRODUCTS","DATE & TIME","MONEY","PERCENTAGE","RATIO","VOLUME","CORPORATE ACTIONS","MARKET EVENTS","POSITIVE","NEGATIVE","EQUITIES","BONDS","REGULATIONS"],"annotations":[["Description\r\nWays and\r\nmeans\r\nadvances\r\n(WMA) are\r\ntemporary\r\nliquidity line\r\ngiven by the\r\ncentral bank\r\nto the\r\ngovernment to\r\nmeet short-\r\nterm ...\r\nWith no upper\r\nlimit, the\r\ninterest rates\r\nin the platform\r\ncan go as\r\nhigh as 35 per\r\ncent, on a\r\nreducing\r\nbalance\r\nBesides\r\nchallenges\r\nfaced by\r\nwholesale\r\nNBFC in\r\nparticular, the\r\ncredit costs\r\n(amount to be\r\nprovided for\r\nstressed\r\nassets), are ...\r\nAccording to\r\nan Edelweiss\r\nreport, Rs 1\r\ntrillion non-\r\nconvertible\r\ndentures\r\n(NCDs) and\r\nRs 1.2 trillion\r\ncommercial\r\npapers (CPs)\r\nare ...\r\nOn a\r\nstandalone\r\nbasis, as of\r\nDecember\r\nquarter, the\r\nlender had a\r\ncapital\r\nadequacy\r\nratio of 18.2\r\nper cent, with\r\ntier 1 capital\r\nat ...\r\nTo tap RBI\r\nrefinance\r\nwindow for\r\nfunding to\r\nRRBs etc\r\nAlthough the\r\ngovernment\r\nhas allowed\r\nNBFCs, HFCs\r\nto start\r\noperations,\r\nthey have not\r\nallowed\r\nresumption of\r\noperations in\r\nhotspots ...\r\n\fLenders to\r\nface central\r\nbank's\r\ncensure;\r\nboard meet in\r\nMay seen\r\nleading to\r\nfresh\r\nmeasures\r\n\r\nBanks will\r\nhave to\r\ncategorise the\r\nmoratorium\r\nloans as\r\nspecial\r\nmention\r\naccounts\r\n(SMA)\r\nwherein loans\r\nare in the 0-\r\n90 days\r\noverdue ...\r\nOn Friday, the\r\nRBI said it will\r\nconduct the\r\nsecond\r\ntranche of\r\ntargeted long-\r\nterm repo\r\noperation\r\n(TLTRO 2.0)\r\nfor an\r\naggregate ...\r\nIt is one of the\r\nmost coveted\r\njobs in the\r\nIndian\r\nbanking\r\nsector and\r\nmarket\r\nwatchers are\r\nkeenly\r\nawaiting who\r\nwill be the\r\nchosen ...\r\nGolden\r\nJubilee Hotels\r\nPvt Ltd is a\r\npublic-private\r\npartnership\r\n(PPP) with the\r\nDepartment of\r\nTourism and\r\nYouth\r\nAdvancement,\r\nTourism ...\r\nHowever,\r\nthere was no\r\nclarity on\r\nwhether the\r\nfinance\r\ncompanies\r\nthat borrow\r\nfrom banks\r\nwould get the\r\noption to\r\ndelay\r\npayments to\r\n...\r\n\fIt had\r\nreported a\r\npre-tax profit\r\nof Rs 8,954.38\r\ncrore in the\r\nsame period\r\nlast financial\r\nyear\r\n(Q4FY19).\r\nA senior\r\nexecutive of a\r\npublic sector\r\nbank said the\r\nIBA's\r\nmanagement\r\ncommittee\r\nmeeting would\r\ndiscuss the\r\nissue of giving\r\na ...\r\n\r\nUnless\r\ndemand\r\nrevives,\r\nindustry\r\nexperts say\r\nthe move may\r\nnot be very\r\neffective\r\nThe branches\r\nwill function\r\nas usual and\r\nwill adhere to\r\nall instructions\r\nlaid down by\r\nthe state\r\ngovernments\r\nfor corporates\r\n...\r\nRBI has put\r\nthe ball in\r\nbanks' court\r\non the\r\nmoratorium\r\nissue\r\nCalls for\r\neconomic\r\npackage for\r\ndistressed\r\nsectors\r\ncontinue\r\nRBI by\r\nreducing\r\nreverse repo\r\nrate by 25\r\nbasis points\r\nhas sent clear\r\nsignals to\r\ndeploy that\r\nmoney - either\r\nby investing\r\nmarkets ...\r\nThe RBI has\r\nindicated that\r\nit expects\r\ninflation to\r\ncome down\r\nby\r\nSeptember,\r\nwhich means\r\nthat more rate\r\ncuts are in the\r\noffing\r\n\fRBI governor\r\nis walking a\r\ntightrope,\r\nsays a former\r\nchief\r\nstatistician\r\nEarlier, the\r\nRBI had\r\nreduced the\r\nrepo rate to a\r\n15-year low of\r\n4.40 per cent\r\nby\r\nannouncing a\r\nsteep cut of\r\n75 basis\r\npoints on ...\r\nThe banks are\r\nexpected to\r\nstart credit\r\noperations\r\nfrom April 20,\r\nin a bid to\r\nhelp a\r\nstaggered\r\nrestart of the\r\neconomic\r\nactivities\r\nThe first\r\nTLTRO facility\r\ntook place on\r\nMarch 27, and\r\nso far Rs 1\r\ntrillion has\r\nalready been\r\ndeployed.\r\n\f\f",{"entities":[[13,45,"PRODUCTS"],[92,104,"ORG"],[114,124,"ORG"],[231,243,"PERCENTAGE"],[312,316,"ORG"],[426,435,"ORG"],[445,459,"MONEY"],[460,495,"BONDS"],[501,516,"MONEY"],[518,542,"PRODUCTS"],[585,602,"DATE & TIME"],[609,615,"ORG"],[623,647,"RATIO"],[651,665,"PERCENTAGE"],[673,687,"MONEY"],[704,707,"ORG"],[744,748,"ORG"],[768,778,"ORG"],[793,798,"ORG"],[800,804,"ORG"],[915,930,"ORG"],[942,952,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[957,960,"DATE & TIME"],[979,994,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[998,1003,"ORG"],[1019,1052,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[1118,1129,"DATE & TIME"],[1147,1153,"DATE & TIME"],[1160,1163,"ORG"],[1191,1260,"MARKET EVENTS"],[1330,1353,"ORG"],[1428,1459,"ORG"],[1511,1557,"ORG"],[1622,1640,"ORG"],[1660,1665,"ORG"],[1758,1776,"MONEY"],[1798,1828,"DATE & TIME"],[1857,1876,"ORG"],[1887,1892,"ORG"],[1894,1924,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[2029,2056,"NEGATIVE"],[2153,2171,"ORG"],[2177,2187,"ORG"],[2194,2197,"ORG"],[2220,2225,"ORG"],[2242,2259,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[2326,2329,"ORG"],[2344,2362,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[2366,2382,"PERCENTAGE"],[2393,2430,"POSITIVE"],[2472,2475,"ORG"],[2509,2532,"MARKET EVENTS"],[2538,2547,"DATE & TIME"],[2568,2583,"POSITIVE"],[2695,2698,"ORG"],[2704,2726,"MARKET EVENTS"],[2749,2762,"PERCENTAGE"],[2796,2812,"PERCENTAGE"],[2825,2830,"ORG"],[2849,2873,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"],[2880,2888,"DATE & TIME"],[2965,2986,"MARKET EVENTS"],[3003,3011,"DATE & TIME"],[3025,3039,"MONEY"]]}]]}